{
"q1": {
    "id": "q1",
    "question": "What was the name of the talking car in the television show 'Knight Rider'?",
    "answers": [
      "HAL",
      "BENDER",
      "KITT",
      "JEEVES"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "KITT"
  },
  "q2": {
    "id": "q2",
    "question": "Tilda Swinton plays the role of which character in the Marvel Cinematic Unvierse?",
    "answers": [
      "Agent Peggy Carter",
      "Rocket Raccoon",
      "Valkyrie",
      "The Ancient One"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Ancient One"
  },
  "q3": {
    "id": "q3",
    "question": "Who won the 2014 Academy Award for Best Leading Actor for playing the role of Stephen Hawking in 'The Theory of Everything'?",
    "answers": [
      "Eddie Redmayne",
      "Steve Carell",
      "Bradley Cooper",
      "Benedict Cumberbatch"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Eddie Redmayne"
  },
  "q4": {
    "id": "q4",
    "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'Follows the rise and fall of a stock-broker living the high life.'",
    "answers": [
      "Django Unchained",
      "The Wolf of Wall Street",
      "Up",
      "Snatch"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Wolf of Wall Street"
  },
  "q5": {
    "id": "q5",
    "question": "What are The Simpsons Halloween specials known as?",
    "answers": [
      "Spooky Springfield",
      "The Halloween Haunt",
      "Evergreen Menace",
      "Treehouse of Horror"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Treehouse of Horror"
  },
  "q6": {
    "id": "q6",
    "question": "Which wizard was portrayed by Christopher Lee in 'The Lord Of The Rings'?",
    "answers": [
      "Saruman",
      "Gandalf",
      "Radagast",
      "Merlin"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Saruman"
  },
  "q7": {
    "id": "q7",
    "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'The daughter of a plantation owner conducts a romance with a roguish profiteer.'",
    "answers": [
      "Downfall",
      "My Neighbour Totoro",
      "Gone with the Wind",
      "Up"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Gone with the Wind"
  },
  "q8": {
    "id": "q8",
    "question": "Which film contains the character Oda Mae Brown",
    "answers": [
      "Apocalypse Now",
      "Ghost",
      "Blue Velvet",
      "Terms of Endearment"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Ghost"
  },
  "q9": {
    "id": "q9",
    "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A maverick teacher emboldens his students to new heights of self-expression.'",
    "answers": [
      "Raging Bull",
      "Modern Times",
      "The Wizard of Oz",
      "Dead Poets Society"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Dead Poets Society"
  },
  "q10": {
    "id": "q10",
    "question": "Which actor plays the role of Michelle \"MJ\" Jones-Watson in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
    "answers": [
      "Elizabeth Olsen",
      "Hayley Atwell",
      "Zendaya",
      "Karen Gillan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Zendaya"
  },
  "q11": {
    "id": "q11",
    "question": "Which actor plays the role of Bucky Barnes in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
    "answers": [
      "Sebastian Stan",
      "Stellan Skarsgård",
      "John Slattery",
      "Jeff Goldblum"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Sebastian Stan"
  },
  "q12": {
    "id": "q12",
    "question": "In the Marvel Cinematic Unvierse, which character is played by Karen Gillan?",
    "answers": [
      "Eitri",
      "Nebula",
      "Shuri",
      "Pepper Potts"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Nebula"
  },
  "q13": {
    "id": "q13",
    "question": "What was the name of Dustin Hoffman's character in the 1967 film 'The Graduate'?",
    "answers": [
      "Martin Jackson",
      "Leo Quince",
      "Harold Buck",
      "Ben Braddock"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Ben Braddock"
  },
  "q14": {
    "id": "q14",
    "question": "What is the plot of the movie Memento?",
    "answers": [
      "A mother personally challenges the local authorities to solve her daughter's murder.",
      "A man with short-term memory loss attempts to track down his wife's murderer.",
      "Two grifters team up to pull off the ultimate con.",
      "The story an English officer who successfully united and led the Arab tribes during World War I."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A man with short-term memory loss attempts to track down his wife's murderer."
  },
  "q15": {
    "id": "q15",
    "question": "Who won the 1998 Academy Award for Best Leading Actress for playing the role of Viola De Lesseps in 'Shakespeare in Love'?",
    "answers": [
      "Gwyneth Paltrow",
      "Cate Blanchett",
      "Fernanda Montenegro",
      "Meryl Streep"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Gwyneth Paltrow"
  },
  "q16": {
    "id": "q16",
    "question": "Which film contains the character Jules Winnfield?",
    "answers": [
      "A Streetcar Named Desire",
      "Grease",
      "Gangs of New York",
      "Pulp Fiction"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Pulp Fiction"
  },
  "q17": {
    "id": "q17",
    "question": "Who won the 2000 Academy Award for Best Leading Actor for playing the role of Maximus Decimus Meridius in 'Gladiator'?",
    "answers": [
      "Russell Crowe",
      "Javier Bardem",
      "Tom Hanks",
      "Ed Harris"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Russell Crowe"
  },
  "q18": {
    "id": "q18",
    "question": "Who played the role of James Bond in 'The Man with the Golden Gun'?",
    "answers": [
      "Pierce Brosnan",
      "George Lazenby",
      "Roger Moore",
      "Timothy Dalton"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Roger Moore"
  },
  "q19": {
    "id": "q19",
    "question": "Which director directed 'Inglourious Basterds'?",
    "answers": [
      "Ridley Scott",
      "Spike Lee",
      "Oliver Stone",
      "Quentin Tarantino"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Quentin Tarantino"
  },
  "q20": {
    "id": "q20",
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'The Hunger Games'?",
    "answers": [
      "\"After all, tomorrow is another day!\"",
      "\"May the odds ever be in your favor.\"",
      "\"I'll have what she's having.\"",
      "\"Exercise gives you endorphins. Endorphins make you happy. Happy people just don’t shoot their husbands. They just don’t.\""
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "\"May the odds ever be in your favor.\""
  },
  "q21": {
    "id": "q21",
    "question": "Which director directed '2001: A Space Odyssey'?",
    "answers": [
      "Steven Spielberg",
      "Francis Ford Coppola",
      "Stanley Kubrick",
      "Martin Scorsese"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Stanley Kubrick"
  },
  "q22": {
    "id": "q22",
    "question": "From which London railway station does Harry Potter catch the Hogwart's Express?",
    "answers": [
      "King's Cross",
      "Waterloo",
      "Charing Cross",
      "Paddington"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "King's Cross"
  },
  "q23": {
    "id": "q23",
    "question": "Who was the Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher in 'Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire'?",
    "answers": [
      "Alastor “Mad-Eye” Moody",
      "Remus Lupin",
      "Gilderoy Lockhart",
      "Bartemius Crouch Jr."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Bartemius Crouch Jr."
  },
  "q24": {
    "id": "q24",
    "question": "In which year was Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back first released in theaters?",
    "answers": [
      "1965",
      "1980",
      "1970",
      "1975"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1980"
  },
  "q25": {
    "id": "q25",
    "question": "Who is associated with the address '221B Baker Street, London'?",
    "answers": [
      "Harry Potter",
      "Charles Dickens",
      "Sherlock Holmes",
      "Thomas Hardy"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Sherlock Holmes"
  }
}